Guide to the New York University Archives Audiovisual Collection AV
New York University Archives
- Audiovisual Recordings
  - The NYU Lecture Series - 1978-79: "A Memo to Media: Our Hate/Care Relationship" with Tom Brokaw and Frank Shakespeare. Reel II of II., 1978-09-28; AV280 (Box 7, Reel AV280, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV280)
    Housing annotation: From the Media 78 Conference.
  - The NYU Lecture Series - 1978-79: "Corporate Editorial Advertising, Free Speech and Does Anyone Out There Read Our Stuff?" Reel I of II., 1978-09-28; AV281 (Box 7, Reel AV281, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV281)
  - The NYU Lecture Series - 1978-79: "Corporate Editorial Advertising, Free Speech and Does Anyone Out There Read Our Stuff?" Reel II of II., 1978-09-28; AV282 (Box 7, Reel AV282, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV282)
    Format: 1/4" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 27 min.
  - The NYU Lecture Series - 1978-79: "The Business Media: Ally, Analyst, Apologist or Antagonist?" with Bob Bartley, WSJ; Bob Flaherty, Forbes; and Prof. Irving Kristol, NYU. Reel I of II., 1978-09-27; 1979-03-05; AV283 (Box 7, Reel AV283, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV283)
    Housing annotation: The lecture series program is included with the tape."WNYU BDCST 3-5-79, 8-9 pm" marked on container label in red ink. From the Media 78 Conference.
  - The NYU Lecture Series - 1978-79: "The Business Media: Ally, Analyst, Apologist or Antagonist?" with Bob Bartley, WSJ; Bob Flaherty, Forbes; and Prof. Irving Kristol, NYU. Reel II of II., 1978-09-27; 1979-03-05; AV284 (Box 7, Reel AV284, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV284)
    From the Media 78 Conference.
  - University Broadcast Lab - Fall 1976: "Lance Hayward: His Music, His Magic," produced by Tom Solomon. Reel I of I., 1976-11-01; AV274 (Box 7, Reel AV274, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV274)
    Format: 1/4" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 30 min., Preservation Note: Original recording contains noticeable electronic hum.
    Housing annotations: The series program is included with the tape.
  - University Broadcast Lab - "Woody Gutherie: Dust Bowl Blues Balladeer." Reel I of I., 1975-03-27; AV275 (Box 7, Reel AV275, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV275)
    Housing annotation: "WNYU BDCST 3-27-75, 8:30-9pm" marked on container label in red ink. Produced by Stewart S. Lilker written in ink on container.
  - Belli I: Adam Belli, Dean's Day, NYU Law School., 1973-11-17; AV276 (Box 7, Reel AV276, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV276)
    Format: 1/4" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 35 min.
    Housing annotations: There are two separate hand-written notes included inside the container.
  - The NYU Lecture Series - 1978-79: "A Civil Tongue: Language and Media" with NBC Correspondent Edwin Newman. Reel I of I., 1979-03-12; AV285 (Box 7, Reel AV285, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV285)
    Housing annotation: "WNYU-FM BDCST 3-12-79, 8-9pm" marked on container label in red ink.
  - The NYU Lecture Series - 1978-79: "Interview Technique" with Chuck Rossi and George Maier. Reel I of I., 1978-09-27; 1979-03-12; AV286 (Box 7, Reel AV286, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV286)
    Housing annotation: "WNYU-FM BDCST 3-12-79" marked on container label in red ink. From the Media 78 Conference.
  - The NYU Lecture Series - 1978-79: "The Wire Services: Get It First, Get It Fast, and Get It Right!" with Dottie Brooks, UPI; William Clabby, Dow Jones; and John Cunnif, AP. Reel I of II., 1978-09-28; 1981-04-07; AV287 (Box 7, Reel AV287, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV287)
    Housing annotation: "WNYU-FM Rebroadcast 4-7-81, 7-8pm" marked on container label in red ink. From the Media 78 Conference.
  - The NYU Lecture Series - 1978-79: "The Wire Services: Get It First, Get It Fast, and Get It Right!" with Dottie Brooks, UPI; William Clabby, Dow Jones; and John Cunnif, AP. Reel II of II., 1978-09-28; 1981-04-07; AV288 (Box 7, Reel AV288, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV288)
    Format: 1/4" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 23 min.
  - The NYU Lecture Series - Fall Semester 1982: "The Promise of Prosperity," Joyce Appleby, historian and author. Reel I of II., 1982-12-21; AV289 (Box 7, Reel AV289, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV289)
    Housing annotation: "For air 12/21/82, 8:30-9:30 pm."
  - The NYU Lecture Series - Fall Semester 1982: "The Promise of Prosperity," Joyce Appleby, historian and author. Reel II of II., 1982-12-21; AV290 (Box 7, Reel AV290, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV290)
  - Conference on the Rights of Minors, Part I., 1971-10-22; AV291 (Box 7, Reel AV291, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV291)
    Format: 1/4" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 68 min.
    Housing annotation: Welcome and Opening Remarks. Panel: The Adolescent Youth in an Age-Graded Society.
  - Conference on the Rights of Minors, Part II., 1971-10-22; AV292 (Box 7, Reel AV292, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV292)
    Housing annotation: Panel (continued): The Adolescent Youth in an Age-Graded Society. Panel: The Legal Rights and Disabilities of People Not Yet Passed Their 21st Birthday.
  - Conference on the Rights of Minors, Part III., 1971-10-22; AV293 (Box 7, Reel AV293, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV293)
    Housing annotation: Panel (continued): The Legal Rights and Disabilities of People Not Yet Passed Their 21st Birthday. Panel: The Street Scene.
  - Conference on the Rights of Minors, Part IV., 1971-10-22; AV294 (Box 7, Reel AV294, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV294)
    Housing annotation: Panel (continued): The Street Scene.
  - Conference on the Rights of Minors, Part IX., 1971-10-22; AV295 (Box 7, Reel AV295, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV295)
    Housing annotation: Workshop (continued): Health, Medical, and Psychiatric.
  - Conference on the Rights of Minors, Part X., 1971-10-22; AV296 (Box 7, Reel AV296, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV296)
    Format: 1/4" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 65 min.
    Housing annotation: Workshop: Drugs, Youth, and the Law.
  - Conference on the Rights of Minors, Part XI., 1971-10-22; AV297 (Box 7, Reel AV297, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV297)
    Housing annotation: Workshop (continued): Drugs, Youth, and the Law.
  - Conference on the Rights of Minors, Part XII., 1971-10-22; AV298 (Box 7, Reel AV298, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV298)
    Format: 1/4" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 64 min.
    Housing annotation: The Right of a Child to an Education.
  - 1974 NYU "Goals Conference" - Part 1., 1974-03-01; AV299 (Box 7, Reel AV299, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV299)
    Format: 1/4" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 62 min.
  - 1974 NYU "Goals Conference" - Part 2., 1974-03-01; AV300 (Box 7, Reel AV300, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV300)
  - 1974 NYU "Goals Conference" - Tape 1, 1974-02-26; AV301 (Box 7, Reel AV301, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV301)
    Housing annotation: 1st Speaker - President Hester, 9 am
  - 1974 NYU "Goals Conference" - Tape 2, 1974-02-26; AV302 (Box 7, Reel AV302, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV302)
  - Conference on the Rights of Minors, Part XVI., 1971-10-22; AV336 (Box 8, Reel AV336, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV336)
    Format: 1/4" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 38 min.
    Housing annotation: Panel (cont'd): Youth Advocacy. Concluding Plenary Session.
  - 1974 NYU "Goals Conference" - Opening Plenary Session, Reel 1., 1974-02-28; AV312 (Box 8, Reel AV312, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV312)
    Format: 1/4" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 32 min., Preservation Note: Significant electronic interference captured on tape during original recording.
  - 1974 NYU "Goals Conference" - Opening Plenary Session, Reel 2, 1974-02-28; AV313 (Box 8, Reel AV313, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV313)
    Format: 1/4" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 7 min., Preservation Note: Some electronic interference captured on tape during original recording.
  - The NYU Lecture Series - 1978-79: "Jews in America" with Professor Salo Baron, Columbia University Center of Israel and Jewish Studies. Reel I of II., 1978-10-09; AV314 (Box 8, Reel AV314, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV314)
    Housing annotation: "PGM (COPY) FOR AIR 10-9-78, 8:30-9:30pm" marked on container label in red ink.
  - The NYU Lecture Series - 1978-79: "Jews in America" with Professor Salo Baron, Columbia University Center of Israel and Jewish Studies. Reel II of II., 1978-10-09; AV315 (Box 8, Reel AV315, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV315)
  - The NYU Distinguished Scholars Forum - PGM #14: "Psi Phenomenon and Psychotherapy" with Dr. Mark Stern. Reel I of II., 1978-03-31; AV316 (Box 8, Reel AV316, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV316)
    Housing annotation: "FOR WNYC-AM BDCST, 3-31-78, 2:30-3:30pm"
  - The NYU Distinguished Scholars Forum - PGM #14: "Psi Phenomenon and Psychotherapy" with Dr. Mark Stern. Reel II of II., 1978-03-31; AV317 (Box 8, Reel AV317, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV317)
  - Conference on the Rights of Minors, Part XIII., 1971-10-22; AV333 (Box 8, Reel AV333, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV333)
    Housing annotation: Panel: The Rights of a Child to Seek Gainful Employment When and Where He Feels Fit to Do So.
  - Conference on the Rights of Minors, Part XIV., 1971-10-22; AV334 (Box 8, Reel AV334, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV334)
    Housing annotation: Panel: The Right of a Child to Basic Services.
    Recording features an address by Fr. Bruce Ritter, founder of Covenant House, at 34-minute mark.
  - Conference on the Rights of Minors, Part XV., 1971-10-22; AV335 (Box 8, Reel AV335, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV335)
    Housing annotation: Panel (cont'd): The Right of a Child to Basic Services. Panel: Youth Advocacy.
  - Brookdale Dental Center Dedication Ceremony. Reel I of I., undated; AV323 (Box 8, Reel AV323, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV323)
  - De Mirville. Reel I of III., undated; AV318 (Box 8, Reel AV318, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV318)
  - De Mirville. Reel II of III., undated; AV319 (Box 8, Reel AV319, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV319)
  - De Mirville. Reel III of III., undated; AV320 (Box 8, Reel AV320, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV320)
  - The NYU Lecture Series - 1973 PGM #6: "The Psychological Aspects of Alcohol Addiction" with Dr. Robert Campbell, associate director, department of psychiatry, St. Vincent's Hospital. Reel I of II., 1973-1974; AV324 (Box 8, Reel AV324, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV324)
    Housing annotation: Several different WNYU broadcast program dates are listed and scratched out on container label in red ink.
  - The NYU Lecture Series - 1973 PGM #6: "The Psychological Aspects of Alcohol Addiction" with Dr. Robert Campbell, associate director, department of psychiatry, St. Vincent's Hospital. Reel II of II., 1973-1974; AV325 (Box 8, Reel AV325, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV325)
  - Annual Review of U.N. Affairs. Reel I of II., undated; AV329 (Box 8, Reel AV329, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV329)
    Housing annotation: There is no clear indicator of which is Reel I and which is Reel II. Both tapes have the same title.
  - Annual Review of U.N. Affairs. Reel II of II., undated; AV330 (Box 8, Reel AV330, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV330)
  - The NYU Lecture Series - Spring 76: "The American Revolution of 1776: Origins." Phelps Lectures #1, Dr. Merrill Jensen, Vilas Research Professor of History, Univ. of Wisconsin. Reel I of II., 1973-11-05; 1976-03-15; AV331 (Box 8, Reel AV331, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV331)
    Housing annotation: The lecture series program is included with the tape. "WNYU-FM BDCST 3-15-76, 8:30-9:30pm" marked on container label in red ink.
  - The NYU Lecture Series - Spring 76: "The American Revolution of 1776: Origins." Phelps Lectures #1, Dr. Merrill Jensen, Vilas Research Professor of History, Univ. of Wisconsin. Reel II of II., 1973-11-05; 1976-03-15; AV332 (Box 8, Reel AV332, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV332)
    Housing annotation: "WNYU-FM BDCST 3-15-76, 8:30-9:30pm" marked on container label in red ink.
  - Tape 1 Bayer. Reel I of III., undated; AV339 (Box 8, Reel AV339, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV339)
    Format: 1/4" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 67 min.
  - Tape 1 Bayer. Reel II of III., undated; AV337 (Box 8, Reel AV337, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV337)
  - Tape 1 Bayer. Reel III of III., undated; AV338 (Box 8, Reel AV338, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV338)
  - Tape 2 Bayer. Reel I of IV., undated; AV340 (Box 8, Reel AV340, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV340)
  - Tape 2 Bayer. Reel II of IV., undated; AV341 (Box 8, Reel AV341, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV341)
    Format: 1/4" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 196 min.
  - Tape 2 Bayer. Reel III of IV., undated; AV342 (Box 8, Reel AV342, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV342)
  - Tape 2 Bayer. Reel IV of IV., undated; AV343 (Box 8, Reel AV343, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV343)
    Format: 1/4" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 21 min.
  - Piaget Lecture. Reel I of IV., 1967-03-23; AV344 (Box 8, Reel AV344, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV344)
  - Piaget Lecture. Reel II of IV., 1967-03-23; AV345 (Box 8, Reel AV345, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV345)
  - Piaget Lecture. Reel III of IV., 1967-03-23; AV346 (Box 8, Reel AV346, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV346)
  - Piaget Lecture. Reel IV of IV., 1967-03-23; AV347 (Box 8, Reel AV347, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV347)
    Format: 1/4" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 5 min.
  - Piaget Lecture. Reel I of IV., 1967-03-21; AV348 (Box 9, Reel AV348, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV348)
    Format: 1/4" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 31 min.
  - Piaget Lecture. Reel II of IV., 1967-03-21; AV349 (Box 9, Reel AV349, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV349)
  - Piaget Lecture. Reel III of IV., 1967-03-21; AV350 (Box 9, Reel AV350, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV350)
  - Piaget Lecture. Reel IV of IV., 1967-03-21; AV351 (Box 9, Reel AV351, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV351)
  - Piaget Lecture. Reel I of III., 1967-03-20; AV352 (Box 9, Reel AV352, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV352)
  - Piaget Lecture. Reel II of III., 1967-03-20; AV353 (Box 9, Reel AV353, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV353)
  - Piaget Lecture. Reel III of III., 1967-03-20; AV354 (Box 9, Reel AV354, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV354)
  - "Of Concern: Parenting Problems" with Dr. Lawrence Balter, Coordinator of the Psychoeducational Center, NYU. Guests: Elizabeth Jacobs and Larry Zelnick, NYU Doctoral Students, Reel I of I., 1982-02-17; 1982-02-21; AV383 (Box 9, Reel AV383, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV383)
  - "Trail of Tears - A Conflict of Cultures," Five Selected Segments. Reel I of I., undated; AV384 (Box 9, Reel AV384, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV384)
    Housing annotation: All material copyrighted. 1) Prologue 2) Black Legend 3) Broken Promises 4) Shades of Dickens on the Reservation 5) A Final Dialogue
  - "Uses and Abuses Electronic Media," Part I of 4., undated; AV373 (Box 9, Reel AV373, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV373)
  - "Knowledge", 1980-06-12; AV376 (Box 9, Reel AV376, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV376)
  - "Campaign," Five Segments, Reel #1., undated; AV381 (Box 9, Reel AV381, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV381)
    Housing annotation: 1) 1800 Jefferson, 4:36 2) 1828 Jackso,n 4:56 3) 1840 Wm. Henry Harrison, 4:49 4)1844 Polk, 4:42 5) 1856 Buchanan, 4:40
  - NYU College of Dentistry Anniversary Dinner, Edited. Reel 2., undated; AV364 (Box 9, Reel AV364, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV364)
    Housing annotation: Handwritten breakdown of segments is included with tape.
  - The NYU Lecture Series - Fall Semester 1976-77 PGM #10: "The Perspective of Literature," 10th of 13 on theme, "Perspectives in American Law: The Third Century," delivered by Prof. Ralph W. Ellison. Reel I of I., 1976-11-22; AV386 (Box 9, Reel AV386, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV386)
  - University Broadcast Lab-Audio: "Jae and Ellen in Concert," directed by Rick Benowitz, Reel I of I., undated; AV385 (Box 9, Reel AV385, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV385)
  - Campus Dateline with Herb Livesey 3' Cuts, unknown; AV382 (Box 9, Reel AV382, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV382)
    Housing annotation: 1) "Afterword for Parents" 2) "It Really Is a Different World" 3) "Joe College Is Dead" 4) "The Old Quad Downtown" 5) "Colleges Ideal for Late-Bloomers" 6) "Parents' Survival Kit" 7) "Over-sell at the End of the Rainbow"
  - Conference on the Rights of Minors, Part V., 1971-10-22; AV369 (Box 9, Reel AV369, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV369)
    Housing annotation: Workshop: Health, Medical, and Psychiatric
  - Conference on the Rights of Minors, Part VI., 1971-10-22; AV370 (Box 9, Reel AV370, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV370)
    Housing annotation: Workshop (cont'd): Health, Medical, and Psychiatric
  - Conference on the Rights of Minors, Part VII., 1971-10-22; AV371 (Box 9, Reel AV371, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV371)
  - Conference on the Rights of Minors, Part VIII., 1971-10-22; AV372 (Box 9, Reel AV372, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV372)
  - The NYU Lecture Series - Spring Semester 1983 PGM #4: "The Middle East Evaluated" with Norman Podhoretz, editor of "Commentary" magazine. Reel I of II., 1983-02-01; AV374 (Box 9, Reel AV374, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV374)
    Format: 1/4" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 42 min.
  - The NYU Lecture Series - Spring Semester 1983 PGM #4: "The Middle East Evaluated" with Norman Podhoretz, editor of "Commentary" magazine. Reel II of II., 1983-02-01; AV375 (Box 9, Reel AV375, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV375)
    Format: 1/4" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 16 min.
  - Annual Review of U.N. Affairs #2, 1963-05-14; AV365 (Box 9, Reel AV365, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV365)
  - Annual Review of U.N. Affairs #11, 1963-05-15; AV366 (Box 9, Reel AV366, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV366)
  - Annual Review of U.N. Affairs #12, 1963-05-15; AV367 (Box 9, Reel AV367, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV367)
  - The NYU Lecture Series - Spring Semester 1978 PGM #9: "Reflections on 'The Man Who Cried I Am." Guest: John A. Williams, author and essayist. Reel I of II., 1978-03-20; AV361 (Box 9, Reel AV361, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV361)
    Housing annotations: The lecture series program is included with the tape. "For WNYU BDCST 3-20-78, 8:30-9:30pm" marked on container label in red ink.
  - The NYU Lecture Series - Spring Semester 1978 PGM #9: "Reflections on 'The Man Who Cried I Am." Guest: John A. Williams, author and essayist. Reel II of II., 1978-03-20; AV362 (Box 9, Reel AV362, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV362)
  - NYU Wisdom Bank - Rough Modulated Dub, 8 Cuts, undated; AV378 (Box 9, Reel AV378, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV378)
    Content is duplicated on AV377, but utilizes different takes.
  - NYU Wisdom Bank - 3' Cuts, undated; AV379; Format: 1/4" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 23 min. (Box 9, Reel AV379, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV379)
  - NYU Wisdom Bank - Review Copy, Rough Modulated Dub, 8 Cuts, undated; AV377 (Box 9, Reel AV377, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV377)
    Content is duplicated on AV378, but utilizes different takes.
  - NYU Wisdom Bank - Revised Version. Part 3 of I, undated; AV380 (Box 9, Reel AV380, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV380)
    Housing annotation: Script is included with the tape. 1) Dr. Ethel Alpenfels, 2:33 2) Dean David Oppenheim, 2:24 3) Prof. John Bell, 2:35 4) Dr. Marian Hamburg, 2:38 5) Dr. Bruno Stein, 2:37 6) Dean Daniel Griffiths, 2:39 7) Prof. Owen Rachleff, 2:24
  - Dubbing Master - Yr 2000 Series 2, Reel I of II., AV363 (Box 9, Reel AV363, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV363)
  - Dubbing Master - Yr 2000 Series 2, Reel II of II., AV368 (Box 9, Reel AV368, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV368)
  - Viewpoint International: Puerto Rico as Seen by American Students, 1956; AV422 (Box 10, Reel 422, Box Shared University Archives 116, Cd 12)
    This item has been digitized with funds from New York State.
    Puerto Rico.
  - Campus Editorial: Is Chivalry Dead?, 1956; AV423 (Box 10, Reel 423, Box Shared University Archives 116, Cd 13)
  - Campus Editorial: Freedom of Speech/Viewpoint International: Christmas in Your Country, 1956; AV424 (Box 10, Reel 424, Box Shared University Archives 116, Cd 14)
  - Viewpoint International: Refugees from Behind the Iron Curtain, 1956; AV425 (Box 10, Reel 425, Box Shared University Archives 116, Cd 15)
  - Campus Editorial: Has the U.S. Fulfilled Its Role in the Hungarian Revolt/Viewpoint International: The French Drama, 1957; AV426 (Box 11, Reel 426, Box Shared University Archives 116, Cd 16)
    Duration: 29 minutes, Preservation Note: Multiple bad splices had to be repaired.
  - Campus Editorial: Should Capital Punishment Be Abolished in the U.S./Viewpoint International: The French Novel, 1957; AV427 (Box 11, Reel 427, Box Shared University Archives 116, Cd 17)
    Duration: 29 minutes, Preservation Note: Multiple bad splices had to be repaired; Two different contents recorded in opposite direction - first part digitally reversed.
  - Campus Editorial: Are Athletics Being Overemphasized in Our Colleges and Universities/Viewpoint International: Italian Music, 1957; AV428 (Box 11, Reel 428, Box Shared University Archives 116, Cd 18)
  - Campus Editorial: Should American Policemen Carry Nightsticks Instead of Guns/Viewpoint International: Seminar in Western Europe, 1957; AV429 (Box 11, Reel 429, Box Shared University Archives 116, Cd 19)
    Duration: 29 minutes, Preservation Note: Multiple bad splices had to be repaired
  - Campus Editorial: What Will Be the Outcome of the Middle East Question/Viewpoint International: American Interests in Foreign Study, 1957; AV430 (Box 11, Reel 430, Box Shared University Archives 116, Cd 20)
  - Urban League Presents: Judge Delany, 1959; AV431; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.) (Box 11, Reel 431)
    Duration: 15 minutes, Preservation Note: Some bad splices repaired
  - Urban League Presents: Frank Turner, 1959; AV432; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.) (Box 11, Reel 432)
  - Urban League Presents: A Lawyer Looks at Bigotry, 1959; AV433; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.) (Box 11, Reel 433)
  - Urban League Presents: Organized Labor and Community Services (Part 1), 1959; AV434; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.) (Box 11, Reel 434)
  - Urban League Presents: Organized Labor and Community Services (Part 2), 1959; AV435; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.) (Box 11, Reel 435)
  - Urban League Presents: Do Our Hospitals Discriminate? (Part 1), 1959; AV436; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.) (Box 11, Reel 436)
    Duration: 15 minutes, Preservation Note: Multiple bad splices had to be repaired
  - Urban League Presents: Do Our Hospitals Discriminate? (Part 2), 1959; AV437; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.) (Box 11, Reel 437)
    Duration: 14 minutes, Preservation Note: Some bad splices repaired
  - Urban League Presents: Educational Television, 1959; AV438 (Box 11, Reel 438, Box Shared University Archives 117, Cd 7)
  - Urban League Presents: Switchblade Knives, 1959; AV439 (Box 11, Reel 439)
  - Urban League Presents: Negro History in the School Curriculum, 1959; AV440 (Box 11, Reel 440)
  - Urban League Presents: Equal Opportunity 1959, AV441 (Box 11, Reel 441)
  - Urban League Presents: Negro Influence in American History, 1959; AV442 (Box 11, Reel 442)
  - Urban League Presents: Can Psychiatry Help Juvenile Offenders? (Part 1), 1959; AV443 (Box 11, Reel 443)
  - Urban League Presents: Can Psychiatry Help Juvenile Offenders? (Part 2), 1959; AV444 (Box 11, Reel 444)
  - Urban League Presents: Open Neighborhoods, 1959; AV445 (Box 11, Reel 445, Box Shared University Archives 117, Cd 6)
    Duration: 15 minutes
  - Urban League Presents: Opportunities in Teaching, 1960; AV446 (Box 11, Reel 446)